<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>http://policypolice.in/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://policypolice.in/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://policypolice.in/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://policypolice.in/about/about/</guid>
      <description>This ‘site-name’ is an initiative to educate people about the government policies that has an effect on their day to day life. We are not affiliated and are not part of any kind of political group or party.
Our goal: We want to spread awareness among people as, currently there is no platform where people can get needed information about the government policies in an easy or articulate way. We are providing a healthy platform where people can voice their opinions and engage in active debates about the government policies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BJP Manifesto 2019</title>
      <link>http://policypolice.in/manifesto/bjp_2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://policypolice.in/manifesto/bjp_2019/</guid>
      <description>BJP has realeased their manifesto on 08-04-2019 for the General Elections of 2019 which is going to happen in 7 phases between 11 April to 19 May.
Here, I will note down some of the policies and goals BJP has led down for there 2019 General Elections:
 GOOD GOVERNANCE  We are committed to the idea of simultaneous elections for Parliament, State assemblies and local bodies to reduce expenditure, ensure efficient utilization of government resources and security forces and for effective policy planning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AAP Manifesto 2014</title>
      <link>http://policypolice.in/manifesto/aap_2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://policypolice.in/manifesto/aap_2014/</guid>
      <description>Manifesto - What does manifesto represent. Manifesto is a public statement of someone&amp;rsquo;s policies, views and intention do something which political parties put in front of people before elections.
Why do Political Parities Need Manifesto - Manifesto functions as both a statement of a principles and a bold, sometimes rebellious call to action. By causing people to evaluate the gap between those principles and their current reality, the manifesto challenges assumptions, fosters commitment, and provokes change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Congress Manifesto 2019</title>
      <link>http://policypolice.in/manifesto/congress_2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 22:40:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://policypolice.in/manifesto/congress_2019/</guid>
      <description>Congress was the first political party that released manifesto before General Election of 2019. This election will happen in 7 phases from 11 April to 19 May. Now lets dive into the manifesto of congress, let&amp;rsquo;s see what it is offering to the public :-
 INDUSTRY &amp;amp; JOB  All of the 4 lakh vacancies as on 1 April 2019 in the Central Government, Central Public Sector Enterprises, Judiciary and Parliament will be filled before the end of March 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BJP Manifesto 2014</title>
      <link>http://policypolice.in/manifesto/bjp_2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://policypolice.in/manifesto/bjp_2014/</guid>
      <description>So what does MANIFESTO means - A public declaration of intent, policies, aims, beliefs etc, as issued by the political parties before the election.
Why do Political Parities Need Manifesto - Manifesto functions as both a statement of a principles and a bold, sometimes rebellious call to action. By causing people to evaluate the gap between those principles and their current reality, the manifesto challenges assumptions, fosters commitment, and provokes change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Congress Manifesto 2014</title>
      <link>http://policypolice.in/manifesto/congress_2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:33:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://policypolice.in/manifesto/congress_2014/</guid>
      <description>First Indian General Election Held from 25 Oct 1951 - 21 Feb 1952. No election is complete without political parties talk about there agenda and policy that benefit people. So what does MANIFESTO means - a public declaration of policy and aims, especially one issued before an election by a political party or candidate.
Here, I will list notable policy and few points that congress party had put for the election of 2014:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search</title>
      <link>http://policypolice.in/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://policypolice.in/search/</guid>
      <description> Manticore Search </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>